The basic one is dharma.
In fact, it reflects dharma into two
parts: dharma in books and dharma in the ideas of the
book. And the idea is that this book is dharma. Yes, it
can protect you, that's not true, but the idea of
understanding, understanding two husbands,
that's real protection. Do you use
it or not? That's also different, but this is an
absolute example. But in fact, you need to
use both.
That's how they fail 100%. 4 meditation, when
will your friends come to us, don't rub, you
will be minty root. On this picture, you
need to show
2. 2 types of precious gift. We are the first. This is
book 2. The idea is the same behind this smile.
This picture shows two types of dharma
jewels.
This is a jewel in books and in
consciousness. How many dharma
jewels are there now? I have one, or Lam
Rim, there are masters, Kamala Shila. I'm here,
one, two, three, four. You can count, and here are
three, and the ideas that protect us are a pacifier. Since
such ideas are the three main
paths, the path in Tibetan
is an idea, and the first idea is the first path is
renunciation, this is the understanding that there are problems in life,
that life itself is a problem because it will
end if you think.  That everything is
going well, just wait a little while,
until you have to go to the
doctors every day. I basically didn't
read one article that
conducted research on the
restoration of old people and that it is
impossible to establish the personal illness of elderly people.
You cannot teach diabetes to become a teacher,
diabetes, or cure the brain because
you can cure one disease and
check another. The body begins to
fall apart. The
first thing you need to understand is that in this
world, not everything is going as it should. Our world is
damaged, it is wrong, and we are in
this, in this world, in this reality, there is a
problem.
We all die. This is
not in all realities, so we
just have such a bad area of ​​Minsk. The
second
idea is torture. Reading this, I want to
help other people. The third is
understanding the simplicity of understanding. Handles.
In fact, these are three things. Go and there is a
treasure of dram.
Understanding that the world has problems in the world with
problems that I wanted to help others. And
understanding two husbands, I will tell you all over the
world. We have and mountain. Like when
someone calls you a
fool, you have hernias and nitrates and don't
finish the sentence.